<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BrandonTaylor.tech</title>
    <link>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BrandonTaylor.tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Brandon Taylor</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 13:11:36 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mitmproxy transparent mode</title>
      <link>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/mitmproxy_transparent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 13:11:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/mitmproxy_transparent/</guid>
      <description>Using mitmproxy in transparent mode is useful for applications that do not accept or ignore proxy settings.
This guide is based on a Ubuntu &amp;amp; Windows Machine the instructions of IP forwarding may differ slightly if using another distro.
Linux Setup To enable ipv4 forwarding use the following command
sudo sysctl -w net.ipv4.ip_forward=1 After running the above command you can check to ensure that forwarding is now enable by using the following command</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding Sources Without Apt Key</title>
      <link>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/adding-sources-without-apt-key/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 12:37:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/adding-sources-without-apt-key/</guid>
      <description>The apt-key method of adding gpg keys for repos has been deprecated and will cause a warning message when doing an apt update Using kismets apt source repo I will show you how to take instructions that use the now deprecated apt-key method and change it to use the now supported method for adding repo gpg keys
This is the directions from the kismet site to add their source repo for Debian / Ubuntu based distros I am using a Ubuntu 22.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Phisher - THM</title>
      <link>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/thm_mrphisher/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 22:49:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/thm_mrphisher/</guid>
      <description>There are numerous tools that allow you to extract the macros from a word document without opening it but since those tools don&amp;rsquo;t exist on this box we will have to open up the document with macros disabled (the default on this box)
Upon opening the document we get a warning that the document has macros and they have been disabled (whew)
To view the macros we need to os to tools &amp;gt; macros &amp;gt; edit macros</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>apt-key deprication</title>
      <link>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/apt-key-deprication/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:17:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/apt-key-deprication/</guid>
      <description>While doing an apt update on my Pop_OS! laptop I received the following message
Looking into it I discovered that the gpg key used to sign the updates as trusted was stored in the trusted.gpg store and has been deprecated, so we need to move the gpg key from /etc/apt/trusted.gpg to /usr/share/keyrings/APPKEY.gpg to do this we need to run
sudo apt-key list This will give you a list of your keys we are looking for the key in the /etc/apt/trusted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating your password policy to force passphrases</title>
      <link>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/using_passphrases_ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 15:09:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/using_passphrases_ad/</guid>
      <description>I have recently begun looking at some of the security policies in orgs especially pertaining to passwords. I noticed that typically passwords have to be at least 8 characters and contain a mix of upper and lowercase, numbers, and special chars, but all of those are not required in all environments. In addition to that passwords are set to expire every 3 months. Some environments take this a step further and will remember your last X amount of passwords, this prevents you from using the same few passwords on a cycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Rdp on Kali Linux</title>
      <link>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/setting-up-rdp-on-kali-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 15:57:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/setting-up-rdp-on-kali-linux/</guid>
      <description>My current personal laptop is a 2020 MacBook Air with the M1 SOC as a result of that choice I do have some limitations or rather some challenges to overcome. One of those being the need to run x86 based applications, this is not of concern as far as Windows goes I can just VPN to my home network and use my Desktop for task requiring x86 based code. However for Linux distros specifically in case Kali Linux, remote desktop or RDP takes a little more to get up and running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eJPT Certification</title>
      <link>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/ejpt-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 15:35:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brandontaylor.tech/posts/ejpt-certification/</guid>
      <description>The eJPT certification from INE and eLearnSecurity is awarded to those who pass the exam that is associated with the INE Starter Pass which is a free course you can’t take just for registering a free account with INE (exam not included).
The course is laid out in three parts Introduction, Networking, and Web Applications. The course does a great job of giving you the basics, or a refresher if you are already familiar with basic networking concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
